Hallelujah, you are welcome. When I said Living Water I mean...
being.. you know.. the main thing about his spirit
That they are there..
Cherubim are there.
Cherubim are there...from celestial.
So I don't want you to just leave your seat and walk down there..
Pray with Prophet TB Joshua on the SCOAN Altar
Because you cannot see anything on the floor...does not mean there is nothing there.
If there is nothing here we would not keep so so much space...why are people sitting under the canopy
out there... if there is nothing here...why should we keep a space and Overflow outside there...
we have this plot here..there is a big line here...but we keep this space here for supreme people..
Pray with Prophet TB Joshua At the SCOAN Altar
So when you are living the way of your spirit, determines what you will receive there.
If you are living here and you are say to your colleague: "Please leave me." You receive 'leave me' there too..
Pray with Prophet TB Joshua on the SCOAN Altar
And it is about to leave your seat and to come here and you say you will see ok, come here you will see
Tell your neighbor: "The way you speak...determines what you receive."
Determines what you will see
It is time now to speak what is from your heart.
Faith requires us to speak before we see and feel.
Faith requires us - to do what?
to speak..
Faith requires us to speak before we see or feel.
So right now.. when I finish talking now..
Mind your business.
Tell your wife: "Mind your business."
Tell your husband: "Mind your business."
Tell your children: "Mind your business."
Tell TB Joshua: "Mind your business."
And what is your business here?
Salvation.
We're not agreeing to leave here today. When will TB Joshua come out?. Yeah, look at the time. I don't know...
I hope you will allow me to feed my cock.
Don't bring that idea to the altar here. If your heart is not at his best..
You'll walk there and walk back and you'll be looking at people falling, vomiting, receiving...
and you will ask yourself: "Why on my own is not like that?" Because your heart is not at its best.
On the SCOAN Altar
Tell your neighbor: "What you speak...
determines...
what you will receive."
I speak healing.
I receive healing.
I speak deliverance.
I receive deliverance.
I speak breakthrough.
I receive breakthrough.
I speak prosperity.
I receive prosperity.
I speak salvation.
I receive salvation.
Pray with Prophet TB Joshua On the SCOAN altar
Now...
What will be going on in your heart now...what I speak?
What...will I get?
I should mind my business then. No one can help me. Your yesterday cannot help you now.
Before now cannot help you now. But now.. now.. faith is now.. receive now..
Confess it now.
Believe now.
Mere grace inside this Living Water is breakthrough.
Because I see this breakthrough is what people are yearning for right now.
Since everything seems to be blocked.
I mean.. people appear on people approach everything.
Having this.. having breakthrough..
As I'm standing here now. I'm hearing the cherubim. They are singing breakthrough there.
Breakthrough there.
Thank you. Thank you very much. So please are you ready now?
Your hearts.. what are you saying? Are you now minding your business? Have you forgiven?
Have you given a call to your enemy?
Have you said to your enemy: "Please.. how are you?" Have you done that?
No, no, no, Let me give him two minutes to do that. Give him a call. Give a call to the greatest enemy you have.
Friend, you say you've never greet in life. I'll give you a call and say: "Hi, how are you? I´m praying for you."
Okay, do that, do that, do that...ready to forgive... ready to come to a reconciliation right now.
Because being there, they will ask you.. will ask your heart, have you forgiven?
And if you are now going there to lie to them thinking you are meeting TB Joshua
You come to me sometimes and you´re lying. These people they know if you're lying to them.
It's very serious.
Have you forgiven? Your heart... have you come to reconciliation?
You have come to reconciliation...
Know.. there are many people out there that you say you never have anything to do with them
Indeed.
They have offended you.
You are right. They are wrong. But being a Christian whether we are right or wrong..
we have no right to hold offense. Tell your neighbor: "Whether you are right
or wrong..
you have no right to hold offense.
Can you...can you... in your heart right now..
Right now even if you cannot give a phone call...are you ready to let go..in your heart.
So that's it. You know I said, what you speak determines what you receive.
Okay, are you ready there?
It's another great day here at the SCOAN. Viewers all over the world, you can see our international visitors.
Having the privilege to pay a visit to the altar of God here at the SCOAN.
To pray and also to partake in the Fountain of the Living Water.
Your blessing...rain on me.
You're healing...prayer...
At the SCOAN altar
And right now you can see the people taking out their new Morning Water which is the Fountain of Living Water
at the altar of God and also people praying at the altar pouring their hearts to God
Right there the God Almighty meeting them at a point of their needs. The Spirit of God has already started
working..people are receiving instantaneous deliverance. You can see that man vomiting out poisonous
substances right there on the SCOAN altar.
Right now, wherever you are you can connect by faith in Jesus Name you can see that people are receiving their
own portion of the Living Water right there on the SCOAN altar
and Jesus Christ is taking control over every problem, every situation in their lives.
You can see another woman vomiting out the poisonous substances in her system.
Right there you can see the Holy Spirit is already flushing out all the poisonous substance in her system.
as she prays at the altar of God
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Emmanuel..
After you have received your Living Water..come up to the altar
and pray and enter convenant with God in Jesus Name.
Vomiting poisonous substances
Praying with Prophet TB Joshua´s Bible
See what is happening...a touch of the Bible of the Prophet on the pulpit you can see what is happening
to that woman right now.
Because of the annointing of God. You can see her right now.
She's under the annointing of the Holy Spirit and the Man of God has said, we should go up hill. That is, at the top
that is at the top most part of the altar and enter a covenant with God Almighty.
Pray and enter a covenant with God before you come down after fetching your Living Water.
There is an added blessing of God Almighty in today's wonderful experience.
Somebody is vomiting out blood and poisonous substances as the Spirit of God is flushing out
every sickness every affliction out of their systems. It is happening here live and direct on the SCOAN altar
here at the SCOAN.
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances on the SCOAN altar
Satan is the altar of sickness and disease.
The power of God only can cast out what Satan has planted.
And that´s why you see them vomiting out and receive your own portion of the Living Water.
Today´s wonderful event will not leave your life the same... an immediate difference
will be experienced in terms of break through, healing, deliverance.
You can see them vomiting out all what Satan has planted in their lives. Watch the screen.
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances on the SCOAN altar
Fire! I have destroyed her life...
I was using her doing many things..
Like what?
Following men......drinking....
I'm a biiiii.......I am the great _______________
You see me.... I am so great....
I entered this child since she was small.
The prophet has given the instruction to pray for her and into in covenant with God and so viewers this is her day
for receiving. There is annointing for you also. Touch your screen and receive in the Name of Jesus Christ.
This is why she has also received her deliverance to the glory of God.
This shows that there is power in the name of Jesus. The presence of God is here.
Thank you Jesus for my deliverance. Thank you Lord for setting me free. Thank you Jesus. Thank you Jesus.
These are the poisonous substances behind their afflictions, behind their problems,
behind the situation that they are experiencing in life.
But right now they are vomiting out here on the SCOAN altar
The Spirit of God Himself has come down to set his people free
Viewers all over the world as you are seeing it happening here. It can also happen where you are.
Remember that distance is not a barrier for you to receive.
Touch the screen of your television and the deliverance you see here can happen directly where you are.
Viewers all over the world as you are seeing it happening here. It can also happen where you are.
Remember that distance is not a barrier for you to receive.
Touch the screen of your television and the deliverance you see here can happen directly where you are.
There right now, you can see the woman who is receiving deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ
We can see that the Holy Spirit is exposing the infernal spirits that cause sickness.
The people vomit and are freed from all sickness. There is no doubt that the fire of the Holy Spirit is present
here at the SCOAN.
Viewers there is no distance, no barrier or obstacle for the Power of God
So for today and in faith be blessed. Touch your screen and receive your blessing in the Name of Jesus Christ.
And the annointing found here...only faith is pleasurable to God.
You can see the presence of God on the SCOAN altar and people are vomiting
out poisonous substances out of their systems.
There's another one there...a demon is exposed.
At the altar of the SCOAN in Lagos Nigeria
That woman vomiting are the poisonous substance in her system. So today is your appointment with God.
Be in an attitude of prayer.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances on the SCOAN altar
Demons are manifesting them on the altar as the light of God has exposed every single one of them
Yes where the light of God is darkness has no hiding place.
Right now you can see the evil spirit in the life of that woman manifesting its evil deeds.
I am a devil
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
- yes, I gave a sickness for eight years
I gave her HIV.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I use her body as I want
Stealing, killing and destruction..
She´s my daughter, I came with her.
Before coming here she was attacked. She was seeing evil people... she's not seen their face.
But she sees black like this and they say they want to kill her.
We went to so many places but no solution.
We came here on Friday, today. Thank you Lord, you have delivered her.
You have discovered the devil.
I want to destroy her. I want to destroy her...
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN altar
I entered her body through her grandmother.
Right now you can see the Spirit of God that is forcing out every affliction, every sickness, every problem
in the lives of God's people right now. You can see it happening there on the SCOAN altar, people are
vomiting out poisonous substances
Evil spirits are manifesting and confessing their evil deeds against their wilL.
This woman has received her deliverance from a spirit that confessed that the infernal spirit had entered
through her grandmother and had been wanting to destroy her life. She gave her sickness.
And now we see her delivered by the glory of God. People continue to vomit all types of toxic substances...
poisonous substances that were depositing sicknessess and afflictions in their bodies.
We can see how the root cause of all bitterness is being manifested, vomited and pushed out
by the power of Jesus Christ.
What we are witnessing right now is the real authentic and forceful power of God.
Right now you can see the Spirit of God forcing out every affliction, every sickness, every problem in the lives of
God's people. Right now you can see it happening there on the SCOAN altar, people vomiting out
poisonous substances.
Evil spirits are manifesting and confessing their evil deeds against their will. That is the power of God.
We are many!
Who are you?
I'm from the sea...I married him.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I came to him with food in a dream. I want to destroy his life.
We are many...we are plenty..
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances on the SCOAN altar
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN altar
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN altar
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Praying with Prophet T.B. Joshua´s Bible on the SCOAN altar
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN altar
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN altar
No! Leave me alone!
You can see the manifestation of God's power this older lady
that is under the influence of the Holy Spirit is now vomiting the root cause of her problems
As you saw her manifesting moments ago confessing all that was done through her.
We see how the demon spirit was exposed and she now vomits the cause of her problems that brought her here.
Viewers, we see the people receiving their blessing, their deliverance and progress in Jesus' Name, so can you.
As you can see it happening that the evil spirits are manifesting and just as they are receiving--
What happened to you?
I was praying at the mountain over there.
You were praying, where?
On the other side.
Ok, you were praying at the altar?
I was praying at the altar over here.
What happened to you as you were praying?
I don´t know, I remember I touched the Bible once but I don´t know...
Give thanks to God you are delivered.
Thank you Jesus! Thank you Jesus! I am free! Thank you Jesus!
The instruction before entering the altar was to free their hearts in order to receive all of the blessings of God.
Free from all offense and anger, so today we enter with a free heart to the altar of the SCOAN. People are praying
for God's mercy and favor in their lives and without a doubt they are receiving their healing and deliverance .
Viewers, there is no barrier nor distance for the Power of God and nothing is impossible for Jesus Christ.
So touch your screen because you are here also at the altar of the SCOAN.
So look for the face of Jesus with your heart and receive your own miracle.
International Visitors receing Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
As you can see it is still happening...
Live and direct at the SCOAN alter
Viewers all over the world remember the prayer of the Man of God: "Lord Jesus rain on me..."
"Lord your blessing.. rain on me your healing" And right now as you can see people receiving their deliverance
their healing...be in an attitude of prayer and you also can receive your healing and deliverance in Jesus name.
Manifestation of Evil Sprits on the SCOAN Altar
I got married.....
I´m a spiritual wife...I got into him through a dream
Manifestation of Evil Spirits at the SCOAN Altar
Watch your screen and see what is happening.
That's where you are going. You can see those who have sicknesses, diseases
embedded in the tendon´s, their fluids by demons...the rivers of Living Water is approaching it from the Source.
They start vomiting it out so that they can be free and those who are demon possessed...
Thank you Jesus, I am free! I am free! I'm delivered! Thank you Jesus!
Remember that the Prophet has said that you must free the heart in order to receive the blessings of God.
So that these blessings may become a reality in your life you must leave space in your heart
The prophet has said that you must renounce offense, bitter feelings and anger
Nothing, nothing, nothing! I destroyed everything about her...
What about her health?
Sickness! Sickness! Many, many, many...
How did you get into her?
Through dreams.
International Visitors receive healing at the Altar of the SCOAN
Thank you Jesus I'm delivered my family and my children are free.
There is a demon...that spoke out of that woman as the force of Heaven exposed the demon tormenting her
as the demon spoke out and has been the source of destruction in the life of that woman but today--
the power of God has set her free at the top most part of the altar as the Man of God has instructed.
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance at the Altar of the SCOAN
This woman has confessed her deliverance in Jesus' Name
We see another woman vomiting out poisonous substances.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN Altar
I destroyed him.......I want him......he belongs to me...
You can see the manifestation of evil spirits in lots of the people. This man praying at the altar
has the evil spirits manifesting and also is receiving his deliverances instantly. Look at this gentleman
after his confession, right now, he is about to receive deliverance and so when going to the altar
be in attitude of prayer and make sure you are praying in your hearts for God Almighty to deliver you.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
I just want to thank Jesus Christ, thank you!
As you are approaching the altar, be in an attitude of prayer. You can see the manifestation of the evil spirits
in a lot of the people...these men praying at the altar you can see evil spirits manifesting
and they are also receiving their deliverances instantly.
I want to destroy her....I want to destroy her... I want to get the baby...baby will die if she not delivered....
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN Altar
More and more people are receiving deliverance in the power of the Holy Spirit as they go to the altar to pray.
Many of them before they approach the altar, the Spirit of God exposes that demon inside of them.
Thank you Jesus! I am set free! Thank you Jesus!
Living water is still there for us to fetch for God is about to do something new in our lives.
You can see that woman. See what is happening to her..she's under the influence of the Holy Spirit..
no longer at ease with herself because the Spirit of God wants to take out of her the evil spirit tormenting her
and destroying her life. so let us continue to watch and see what is happening at the altar
as people are going there to pray.
I gave her sickness...stagnation...poverty...
Who are you in this body? Who are you?
Spiritual husband
How did you enter her?
Rituals..
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
At the altar people are receiving deliverance from all forms of infirmities, sicknesses and diseases
in their lives. Give respect to the Spirit of God that is in our midst.
We have seen people vomiting out a different kind of poisonous substances planted in their system.
And we have seen those who are demon-possessed being delivered. To consider, there is another woman
evidence of the presence of God Almighty exposing whatever demon in the life of the people
and setting them free for the salvation of their soul.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits at the SCOAN
Why do you want to kill me? The family! The father's side! I want to kill him! The family wants to kill me!
You must kill him...he wants to make the family great and you cannot forgive him! You cannot forgive him!
We cannot let him go! I told him not to come here but he moved secretly to come here!
How long have you been in his body?!
For five years!
When you receive your wonderful deliverance your wonderful healing at home, please do not forget
to tell us your testimonies. You can send us your testimonies of what God Almighty has done for you.
Through this wonderful blessing on the SCOAN altar.
There is need for you to come back with your good testimony of what the power of God has done in your life
in the cause of today´s service. Do not forget to come back and tell us the mighty things.
Share with the people of God your testimony. We are looking forward to hearing your testimony
of this great miracle that God has brought in your life in the course of this service.
You can see the other lady.. see the expression just a little you can see of the Living Water.
You can see she's no longer at ease with herself because the Spirit of God is in control.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN Altar
Who are you in this body? Who are you?
Spiritual husband.
What else have you done to her? Speak!
I destroyed her career!
She's my older sister we came all the way from Abuja.
She don't have like a boyfriend normally who stay around.
Whenever they propose to her they will step back...disappointment.
I'm really happy. I'm surprised though because we are actually Muslims but now we give our life to Christ.
How did you enter her?
I entered her through a dream!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN Altar
The evil spirit just manifested and said it destroyed her life.
She's been taken to the altar and now she is delivered. How are you?
Fine! Thank you Jesus! Thank you Jesus, I´m delivered!
Do you remember what happened to you?
No...I don´t know...
Congratulations! You are free!
Thank you Jesus! Thank you! I was there.
Explain to us what happened to you?
Fire...I felt something burning inside of me...something started burning inside me..
I feel... I feel...different...I feel something moving inside of me...moving out.
That was when you came to the altar?
Yes.
How are you feeling now?
I'm feeling okay now.
Congratulations, you are free.
Thank you Jesus! Thank you Jesus! My family is free! Thank you Jesus!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN Altar
I will deal with her. She´s my wife! She´s my wife!
I made them to run away! She will become poor. Ask her mother.
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Praying with Prophet TB Joshua's BibleOn the SCOAN Altar
International Visitor's Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Poisonous Substances on the SCOAN Altar
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN Altar
I hate you people!
I hate TB Joshua and his ministry! I hate everything about him!
What have you done to her?
Destruction!
There is nothing!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
Set free in Jesus Name
How are you?
I feel fine..
Do you remember what happened to you?
No I was actually weak..
So, congratulations, you are free.
Thank you Jesus!
As more and more people step onto the altar, they have been delivered from all forms of bondages in their lives.
Remember Moses was told to remove his sandals as he stood on holy ground.
So the altar you are approaching is the holy ground. And as people step onto it, they have been delivered
and the angel of God pulling out every stronghold of Satan in their lives.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits on the SCOAN Altar
I´m a spiritual husband. Her father initiated her to me.
I have destroyed her marriage. I have destroyed her career. Nothing good to her. Nothing!
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
Set Free in Jesus Name
Thank you, Jesus! I am free!
Praying with Prophet TB Joshua's Bible on the SCOAN Altar
I gave her fibroids. Multiple fibroids. I entered her through dreams!
There´s a woman that just manifested right now and right now she has been taken to the Altar
On the altar, she is going to receive her deliverance in Jesus' Name.
I am free. Thank You Jesus. I'm delivered. Thank you. Jesus.
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Poisonous Substances on the SCOAN Altar
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I married her long ago!
See what is happening?
You can see as people step onto the altar
The angel of God exposed the demons in their lives and they take them there and are being delivered.
Set Free in Jesus Name
The Pool on the SCOAN Altar
International Visitors Receiving Deliverance on the SCOAN Altar
Vomiting Poisonous Substances on the SCOAN Altar
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I´m a soldier. Can´t you see my arc?
We seized her...we seized her children...we deported her...from Italy... yes...prostitution...yes...
She did drugs...we destroyed so many things...she did prostitution...she flirted...
The force of Heaven is right there at the altar..
to pull down every stronghold of Satan in the lives of the people.
Exposing the demon that is tormenting them.
The Spirit of God is exposing the demon in the life of that lady.
The power of God is moving mightily on the altar right now, as people are stepping onto the altar,
the Spirit of God is setting them free from all infirmities.
To consider, instant reaction to show that something strange has gone out of her.
Set Free in Jesus Name
There is no hiding place for demons in the Arena of Liberty.
Deliverance is taking place because the power of God is present
The annointing of God is in the Living Water to set the people free.
I want to kill her!
She had a good future.
Her grandmother dedicated her to me.
They take them to the altar for deliverance and they have been delivered. Whatever Satan might have planted
in your spirit, soul and body.
The spirit of God is standing firm right there
to operate from there---to consider instant reaction to show that something strange has gone out of her.
Thank you Jesus, I am free!
TT: Jacqueline Margaret